http://youtu.be/mG7l8QrBhoQ
http://youtu.be/mG7l8QrBhoQ
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: Professor Yerraballi,
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: thầy Yerraballi,
what are we going to learn this time around?
chúng ta sẽ học gì trong lần này?
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: This time around, we've
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: lần này, chúng tôi
enhanced the class from the last offering in spring 2014.
mở rộng thêm 1 số phần cho lớp này so với lần trước vào Xuân 2014.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: OK.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: đồng ý.
What's new?
Mới như thế nào?
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: We've added a lot of additional material.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: tôi thêm nhiều tài liệu.
We found things that students were having trouble with, like for example,
Tôi thấy nhiều học viên gặp vấn đề với, ví dụ,
finite-state machines, and we added material on that.
máy trạng thái, nên tôi thêm tài liệu cho phần đó.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: Yes.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: vâng.
And let's add some material on how to read a data sheet.
và nhớ thêm tài liệu bằng cách nào đọc data sheet.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: Yes.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: vâng.
And also, since this class is really a debugging class,
chưa kể lớp này thực sự là 1 lớp debug
we've added a lot of lecture material on debugging.
nên tôi đã thêm nhiều tài liệu về debug vào.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: Yes.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: vâng.
And the coolest thing we've added this time around
và thứ hay nhất mà tôi đã thêm vào đợt này
is a chapter on wireless communication and the internet of things.
là 1 chương về giao tiếp không dây và internet of things.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: So we're going to use a CC3100 BoosterPack, which
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: vậy chúng ta sẽ xài CC3100 BoosterPack
sits on the LaunchPad.
trên LauchPad.
This will be our vehicle to connect to the internet.
Nó sẽ là công cụ để kết nối tới Internet.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: Yes.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: vâng.
And you've heard of the internet of things, haven't you?
bạn nghe nói tới internet of things chưa?
These are the things.
Chúng sẽ được dạy trong lớp này.
Well, what about certification?
Vậy còn chứng chỉ?
How is that different?
Có gì khác không?
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: So we made certification easier.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: tôi đặt điều kiện lấy chứng chỉ dễ hơn.
In the last offering, we required you to do eight labs out of a possible 11,
Lần trước, tôi đòi bạn phải làm 8 trên 11 lab
and they were sequential.
theo thứ tự.
This time around, we've made it easier.
Lần này, tôi đòi dễ hơn.
So you can pick and choose seven labs out of a possible 13
Bạn chọn và hoàn thành 7 trên 13 lab
and earn your certification.
để đạt được chứng chỉ.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: Yes.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: vâng.
And we learned that people took this class for many reasons,
tôi biết rằng bạn học lớp này vì nhiều lý do,
and they're all good.
lý do nào cũng tốt.
So we encourage you to navigate through our class in whatever manner
Nên tôi khuyến khích bạn hoàn thành hết tài liệu lớp này với cách nào
you feel best suits your needs.
phù hợp nhất với bạn.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: This is kind of like a buffet.
DR. RAMESH YERRABALLI: giống như thưởng thức buffet.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: Yeah, let's go.
DR. JONATHAN VALVANO: vâng, cứ như vậy đi.